

HECTOR VASQUEZ

FRONT END DEVELOPER PBOLÍVAR, VENEZUELA, BOLÍVARIAN REPUBLIC OF +58 4128580282

• DETAILS •

Bolívar
Venezuela, Bolivarian Republic of
+58 4128580282
hvasquezdev@gmail.com

LINKS

https://hectorvasquez.netlify.app/ https://github.com/Hvasquezdev

SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

Vue.js

Vuex

Nuxt.js

Three.js

React.js

Tailwind.Css

Node.js

Git

LANGUAGES

Spanish; Castilian

English

· HOBBIES ·

Learn new things by reading books or blog post, play videogames and also play sports like table tennis or soccer

PROFILE

Passionate and innovative Front end developer with about 2.5 years of professional experience maintaining, building and delivering immersive and engaging user experience, mobile first, accessibility and SEO optimization through Front end web development. Proactive developer learning new things and improving current skills daily. Proeficent with the most modern technologies like modern JavaScript ES6 + / Vue.Js / Nuxt.js also knowledge in S.O.L.I.D. principles and software architecture patterns to keep a good organization and maintainability in the front-end code.

Learning everyday is my path to be a better developer.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend at Café Center Restaurant, Ciudad Bolívar

March 2017 - October 2017

Restaurant online reservation system

- Delivered full responsive web app, cross-browser compatible and accessibility
- · Front-end with vanilla JavaScript and Google material design

Frontend at Policia Municipal, Ciudad Bolívar

April 2018 - November 2018

Traffic taxes system

- · Developed with Vue.js, Bulma.Css
- · Created accessible, optimized and full responsive mobile first web app
- · Connect Front-end with the database made in PHP and MySQL

Full-Stack at Contraloria Municipal del Estado Bolívar, Ciudad Bolívar

February 2019 — December 2019

Intranet web app to send internal messages

- Delivered single page app with responsive (Mobile first), cross-browser compatible and performance optimized
- Developed with modern technologies: Vue.js, Tailwind.Css, Node.Js, Socket.io, MySQL, Express.js

Frontend at Nextreality Digital, Remote

January 2020

Principal Front-End developer to optimize existing web pages and create new web apps

- · Optimize 3D app made with Three.js and A-frame
- · Optimize web pages to better SEO, accessibility and performance
- Create new web apps fully responsive and cross-browser optimized
- · Fix old responsive design in the existing web pages
- · Develop new 3D features with Three.js
- · Connect web apps with an API to fetch and send data

Frontend at Prendea, Remote

November 2020 - Present

Front-end developer to improve and optimize current frontend of the page and also add new features with best practices

- · Optimize web pages to better SEO, accessibility and performance
- · Create new pages fully responsive, cross-browser optimized and accessibility
- · Fix old responsive design in the existing web pages
- · Develop new big frontend features by using best practices
- · Fast iteration and tasks completion to allow the team to make tests
- · Refactor and improve current code and frontend architecture
- · Connect web apps with an API to fetch and send data

EDUCATION

Ingeniería Informática, Intitulo Universitario de Tecnología del Estado Bolívar, Ciudad Bolívar

2015 - January 2020

COURSES COURSES

Arquitecto FrontEnd, Platzi

February 2019

Carrera de JavaScript, Platzi

January 2020

Carrera de Vue.Js, Platzi

March 2019

Intermediate React.js, Frontend Masters

March 2020

JavaScript Hard Parts, Frontend Masters

April 2020

Introducción al Desarrollo Web: HTML y CSS, Google

June 2017